aq.edu.ph 2018-11-24

# Legalities -University of Santo Tomas Legazpi

Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement**

Aquinas-University takes the privacy of its users seriously. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our users in accordance with worldwide practices for customer privacy and data protection. Aquinas-University will not release your personal data to any third parties without your consent or as required by law.

**Information Collected**

We collect personal information from you through the use of inquiry and registration forms and every time you e-mail us your details. We also collect information automatically about your visit to our site. The information obtained in this way, which includes demographic data and browsing patterns, is only used in aggregate form.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. We use customer contact information from the registration form to contact the member when necessary and to provide regular information on Aquinas-University Website. Users may opt-out of receiving mailings.

**Use of Personal Information**

We process personal information collected via www.aq..edu.ph for the purposes of: 

  * providing a personalised service
  * conducting market research surveys
  * providing you with information about Aquinas-University

**Use of Cookies**

We use "cookies" to identify you when you visit www.aq.edu.ph, and to build up a demographic profile. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information back from the browser. If you are uncomfortable with cookie technology, you have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies.

**Choice/opt-out**

You may receive periodic e-mail newsletters from us. These newsletters contain information on new features and facilities of note at the web site. Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us directly.

**Internet-based Transfers**

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing the www.aq.edu.ph site and communicating electronically with us you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.

The Privacy Policy Statement does not apply to Third Party Sites.

**Changes to these Terms**

Aquinas-University reserves the right, at its discretion, to make changes to any part of the Site. Due to its policy of updating and improving the site, Aquinas-University may wish to change these Terms (including those relating to your use of the Content). When terms are changed, we will notify you by e-mail or by publishing details of those changes by including them at the end of these Terms (see "Changes to these Terms"). If you use the Site after we have published or notified you of the changes, you are agreeing now to be bound by those changes. If you do not agree to be bound by those changes, you should not use the Site any further after they are published at the end of these Terms or after you receive notice of them.

**General**

You may not assign, sub-license or otherwise transfer any of your rights under these terms. If any provision of these Terms is found to be invalid by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of that provision will not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of these Terms, which shall remain in full force and effect. Failure by either party to exercise any right or remedy under these Terms does not constitute a waiver of that right or remedy. Headings in these Terms are for convenience only and will have no legal meaning or effect.

**Contacting Aquinas-University**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, or the practices of this site, please contact us.
